{
    "id": "10258b27a24a4b55a35d82255071da0a",
    "title": "Articles And Determiners Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "65407e1a95574403bb98154df6cc6ba6",
            "title": "Articles And Determiners Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Yesterday I had …………………….. strange experience.",
                    "description": "Use 'a' to mean one.",
                    "answers": [
                        "a",
                        "the",
                        "some",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I saw ……………………. German tourists in the store.",
                    "description": "Use some in affirmative sentences. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "a",
                        "some",
                        "any"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has ………………………….. keen eye for detail.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "a",
                        "the",
                        "some"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was ……………………… only child of …………………….. rich merchant.",
                    "description": "Write 'the only child'. A rich merchant means any rich merchant. The rich merchant means a particular merchant. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "the, a",
                        "a, a",
                        "the, the"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………………… person who died yesterday was ……………………… heart patient.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "The, a",
                        "a, a",
                        "a, the"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………….. film that we saw yesterday was interesting.",
                    "description": "We are talking about a particular film here hence use the.",
                    "answers": [
                        "The",
                        "A",
                        "Some"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………………… tea is very strong. You must add ………………………. more milk to it.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "A, some",
                        "The, some",
                        "The, the"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Can I have ……………………… apples?",
                    "description": "Some or a few is possible here.",
                    "answers": [
                        "some",
                        "an",
                        "few",
                        "a few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "I saw ……………………. elephant in ……………………. zoo.",
                    "description": "An elephant means 'one' elephant. It can be any elephant. When we say the elephant, we are talking about a particular elephant. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "a, the",
                        "an, the",
                        "the, the"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Don’t make ………………………. noise. I must get …………………….. sleep.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "any, some",
                        "some, any",
                        "any, any"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "People ride camels in ………………………… desert.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "a",
                        "the",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "There is ……………………. school for …………………….. deaf in this city.",
                    "description": "The deaf means all deaf people. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "a, the",
                        "a, a",
                        "the, the"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}